hello my name is Paul soo welcome to
你好，我叫保罗，欢迎来到
this screencast of the g1 garbage
这个g1垃圾的截屏视频
collector there's a lot of information
收藏家那里有很多信息
already available on g1 but since G 1
在g1上已经可用，但是从G 1开始
will become the default collector for
将成为默认的收集器
JDK 9 I'd like to take this opportunity
JDK 9我想借此机会
to give a high-level introduction to the
对此进行高层次的介绍
collector due to time constraints this
收藏家由于时间的限制这
will be a very basic overview but more
将是一个非常基本的概述，但更多
detail than my information is available
比我的信息更详细
a little bit about myself I've been
关于我自己的一些事
working with Java and the open JDK
使用Java和开放式JDK
community for the past 18 years
过去18年的社区
primarily in the micro Edition space
主要在微型版空间
currently I manage the hotspot garbage
目前，我管理热点垃圾
collection team here at Oracle today
今天的甲骨文公司收集团队
we'll start with a brief introduction to
我们将从简要介绍开始
the variety of collectors currently
当前收藏家的种类
available in hotspot before we're moving
在我们出发之前可以在热点找到
into g1 specifics these are the
到g1细节中，这些是
collectors currently supported in
当前支持的收集器
hotspot serial is intended to address
热点序列旨在解决
use cases where memory footprint is
用例中内存占用量是
critical parallels should be the optimal
关键并行应该是最佳的
choice in most situations where
在大多数情况下的选择
throughput is important CMS is built
吞吐量很重要内置CMS
with a focus on latency but is being
着重于延迟，但正在
deprecated beginning in JDK 9 since for
从JDK 9开始不推荐使用，因为
most applications g1 should provide a
大多数应用程序g1应该提供
better overall experience g1 is intended
旨在提供更好的总体体验
to deliver a balance between throughput
在吞吐量之间取得平衡
and latency while not suffering from
和潜伏期，而不患上
fragmentation as mentioned g1 is now the
g1提到的碎片现在是
default collector for JDK knowing it was
JDK的默认收集器
introduced as an experimental flag in
作为实验性标志引入
1614 and became a fully supported
1614年并得到完全支持
collector in 7u 4 as stated above the
如上所述的7u 4中的收集器
goal of g1 is to provide a balance
g1的目标是提供平衡
between throughput and latency the
在吞吐量和延迟之间
default pause target for g1 is set at
g1的默认暂停目标设置为
200 milliseconds by adjusting this value
调整此值200毫秒
users can tune g1 to provide either
用户可以调整g1以提供
lower latency or higher throughput with
更低的延迟或更高的吞吐量
a higher value providing higher
更高的价值提供更高的价值
throughput at the expense of higher
以更高的吞吐量为代价
overall latency or a lower value of
总延迟或较低的值
providing lower throughput and lower
提供较低的吞吐量和较低的
latency there are three properties that
延迟有以下三个属性
are needed to allow g1 to collect
允许收集g1
objects at finer granularity x' dividing
细度为x'的对象的划分
the heap into smaller regions knowing
将堆分成较小的区域
which objects are live within these
这些对象中存在哪些对象
regions and keeping track of the
区域并跟踪
pointers between these regions in the
这些区域之间的指针
serial and parallel collectors the heap
串行和并行收集器堆
is divided into only two or three
分为两个或三个
regions
地区
with g1 the heap is divided into
与g1堆分为
multiple smaller regions usually around
通常在附近的多个较小区域
2000 regions or so it uses these regions
2000个左右的区域使用这些区域
to achieve a finer granularity on how
以获得更好的粒度
much garbage to collect at each GC pause
每个GC暂停时要收集很多垃圾
unlike serial and parallel the marking
与串行和并行标记不同
phase of G 1 is done concurrently this
G 1的相位同时完成
allows G 1 to find all live objects
允许G 1查找所有活动物体
without stopping the java application
无需停止Java应用程序
objects can be marked in multiple
可以标记多个对象
regions at the same time in order to
地区同时
move objects from one region to another
将对象从一个区域移动到另一个区域
you need to know the pointers pointing
您需要知道指向的指针
to those objects G 1 keeps track of the
G 1跟踪那些对象
pointers between regions in order to
区域之间的指针以
avoid leaving a stale pointer on the
避免将过时的指针留在
heap G 1 can decide to collect a few
G 1堆可以决定收集一些
regions at a time by doing so it can
一次可以做到区域
limit the number of objects being
限制对象的数量
processed resulting in lower pauses
已处理，从而降低了暂停时间
relative to other collectors g1 has more
相对于其他收藏家g1有更多
data on the state of objects in the heap
有关堆中对象状态的数据
before of collection begins giving it
收集之前开始给予
more control over the length of the
对长度的更多控制
pauses as G 1 begins a collection G 1
在G 1开始收集G 1时暂停
needs at least one empty region to move
需要至少一个空白区域才能移动
live objects into a set of regions is
将活动对象划分为一组区域是
selected based on the heuristics such as
根据启发式方法（例如
the amount of live data how much of the
实时数据量
heap is free and the posit argot the
堆是免费的，并且在正位置
live objects from the selected regions
选定区域的活动对象
are moved into the empty region freeing
被移入空区释放
the memory from the original regions the
来自原始区域的内存
heap is now more compact there have been
堆现在更紧凑了
a number of significant improvements in
在以下方面的许多重大改进
G 1 since JDK 8
自JDK 8起G 1
there are numerous changes but 5
有很多变化，但5
significant improvements are string
重大改进是字符串
deduplication class unloading after a
重复数据删除类卸载后
concurrent cycle eager reclamation of
并发循环渴望回收
humongous objects adaptive start of a
大型物体自适应开始
concurrent cycle and more effective
并发周期更有效
pauses more detailed information on each
暂停每个上的更详细的信息
of these is available in the release
其中的可用版本
notes and tuning guides for their
笔记和调音指南
respective releases here are some links
这里的各个版本是一些链接
for more information on gdk9 you can
有关gdk9的更多信息，您可以
download JDK 9 from Oracle comm
从Oracle comm下载JDK 9
participate in discussions on the open
参加公开讨论
JDK mailing lists or follow us on
JDK邮件列表或关注我们
Twitter for news and updates
Twitter的新闻和更新